mayplaces.com 2010-10-07

# Privacy Policy :: MayPlaces

Privacy Policy

When you submit a website to our directory or list a property in Upload a property section, we collect certain information for the agents/individuals or the companies registering with us.  
You agree to accept our Privacy policy.  
The private information we collect is kept strictly confidential.  
We will not use your personal details in any way without your permission.

What information we collect?

Company, agent/individual's name  
E-mail address  
Postal address  
Telephone or/and mobile phone  
IP address  
URL address

Why we collect this information?

We collect these private details for contact purpose only. We may send you information about coming changes on our website; contact you in case of termination of a contract, require rectification of material, submitted by you and other purposes. In case you do not wish to receive this information, you may unsubscribe at any time from our Newsletter form. We also automatically collect IP addresses, which we may use for detecting problems on our server; we do not collect information that can be used to identify any individual.

Links to third parties

MayPlaces.com contains links to other websites. You access them at your own risk. We do not control the content and design of other websites; therefore we take no responsibility for their contents. You must understand that third party products, services and information are not provided or endorsed by us and your legal relationship is with the third party supplier only.  
You should read the terms and conditions of use and the privacy policy of any website you access trough our directory. We can not be held liable over the personal details requirements from the websites on our directory.

Third parties partnership

By submitting to MayPlaces.com you agree that your contact details may be passed on to third parties for permission marketing, unless you notify us that you do not wish to receive this information. This means that your details could be used by our partners in order to send you offers and information about their businesses.

What will happen in case we sell our business?

If we sell our website, respectively the services we provide, your details may be passed on to the new owner. This does not infringe on your privacy rights.

General

MayPlaces.com makes any possible endeavor to protect your personal data from external aggression.  
When providing information to an estate agent/ individual through our web site, this information will be subject to the respective estate agent which may not conform to our privacy policy.

Internet is a global infrastructure and no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. This could lead to disruption in the data protection for which MayPlaces.com can not be hold liable.  
By submitting and contributing to MayPlaces.com you agree with the conditions set out in this policy. We advise you to revise them regularly as we may change them from time to time.
